<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/assets/xslt/atom.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="/assets/css/atom.css" ?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/</id>
	<title>MALOT</title>
	<updated>2021-01-30T04:04:19+01:00</updated>

	<subtitle>The EU MSCA Individual Fellowship</subtitle>

	
		
		<author>
			
				<name>Huan Li</name>
			
			
			
		</author>
	

	<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />

	<generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator>

	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/career%20development/2-pedagogy/</id>
			<title>University Pedagogy Training Start</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/career%20development/2-pedagogy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="University Pedagogy Training Start" />
			<updated>2021-01-29T00:00:00+01:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary></summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/career%20development/2-pedagogy/">&lt;p&gt;Last year in April I received an offer of Assistant Professor at the Department of Computer Science at Aalborg University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a follow-up, the university pedagogy training program is starting this year and for me it is anticipated to finish the training program within one year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this year, I will attend five compulsory courses and some selected courses, and finish a pedagogy report that addresses some specific issues in my teaching activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to finishing the training in a good shape.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="career development" />
			
			
				<category term="career development" />
			

			<published>2021-01-29T00:00:00+01:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-covid-iot/</id>
			<title>New COVID Survey Paper Published</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-covid-iot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New COVID Survey Paper Published" />
			<updated>2021-01-29T00:00:00+01:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Our COVID survey paper is now released at arXiv</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-covid-iot/">&lt;p&gt;Our survey paper &lt;em&gt;Impact of COVID-19 on Adoption of IoT in Different Sectors&lt;/em&gt; is now released at &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.07196&quot;&gt;arXiv&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abstract of this paper is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;COVID-19 has disrupted normal life and has enforced a substantial change in the policies, priorities and activities of individuals, organisations and governments. These changes are proving to be a catalyst for technology and innovation. In this paper, we discuss the pandemic’s impact on the adoption of the Internet of Things (IoT) in various broad sectors namely healthcare, smart homes, smart buildings, smart cities, transportation and industrial IoT. Our analysis of this impact on IoT adoption is based on interviews with many industry experts, a thorough research literature review and a careful examination of reports from leading consulting firms. For each of these sectors, we also provide the details of recent initiatives taken in the wake of COVID-19. We also highlight challenges that need to be addressed and important research directions that will facilitate accelerated IoT adoption in these sectors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This survey contains the most recent research papers about how IoT is incorporated into and affected by COVID-19 in vertical sectors such as healthcare, smart homes, smart buildings, smart cities, transportation, and industrial IoT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This paper has been submitted to IEEE Internet of Things Journal.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2021-01-29T00:00:00+01:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/1-quarter-progress/</id>
			<title>Quarter 1 Project Report</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/1-quarter-progress/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quarter 1 Project Report" />
			<updated>2020-10-15T00:00:00+02:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Q1 Progress Summary</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/1-quarter-progress/">&lt;p&gt;A quarter of the project’s time has passed. During this six months, we have been severely affected by COVID-19. The progress in the Q1 of the project includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Two survey papers (one has been finished and the other is still ongoing). The literature review is the first and the most fundamental part of this project’s research work. At present, a survey about COVID-19’s impact on IoT adoption is almost finished and will be submitted to IEEE Internet of Things Journal, and the other one on LoT data quality management is still developing;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Data Management Plan (DMP). The DMP that defines the collection, management and maintenance of the project data has been finished and submitted to the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Preliminary Career Development Plan (CDP). The CDP has been roughly finished and a discussion with supervisors will be carried out later. For career development, a position of Assistant Professor has been obtained from the Department of Computer Science at AAU. In addition, I have served as the session chair of VLDB 2020 and the external reviewers for several top conferences during this period. Preliminary academic collaboration with Monash, SDU (China), and  BUPT(China) has been established.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Deep participation of teaching activities at AAU CS department, including supervision of several groups and co-lecturing of a course. Moreover, the university pedagogy courses have been enrolled and will be started at the beginning of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Establishment of project website and social media accounts including GitHub and Twitter to disseminate research outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q2 will focus on finalizing the second survey paper, and the first regular research paper about data quality control.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="project management" />
			
			
				<category term="project management" />
			

			<published>2020-10-15T00:00:00+02:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/</id>
			<title>Plans of July 2020</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plans of July 2020" />
			<updated>2020-06-30T00:00:00+02:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>The task planning of July 2020.</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/">&lt;p&gt;The plan of this month include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;discuss with the supervisor and finish the career development plan.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;start to write a survey paper about IoT data management and data quality control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="project management" />
			
			
				<category term="project management" />
			

			<published>2020-06-30T00:00:00+02:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/</id>
			<title>Project Website is Now Online</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Website is Now Online" />
			<updated>2020-06-30T00:00:00+02:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>I am happy to announce that the project website is currently available.</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/">&lt;p&gt;Today is the last day of June, and I am very happy to announce that the project website is available from now on. We will continue to publish any news and results in this venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website is powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;JEKYLL&lt;/a&gt; based on the theme &lt;a href=&quot;http://phlow.github.io/feeling-responsive/&quot;&gt;FEELING RESPONSIVE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="dissemination" />
			
			
				<category term="dissemination" />
			

			<published>2020-06-30T00:00:00+02:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/get-into-implementation/</id>
			<title>Get into MSCA Implementation</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/get-into-implementation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Get into MSCA Implementation" />
			<updated>2020-04-08T00:00:00+02:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>I am excited and looking forward to starting my MSCA project next week. I have read a documentation about how to implement the MSCA. I would like to share some useful information and also keep them as a memorandum.</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/get-into-implementation/">&lt;p&gt;I am excited and looking forward to starting my MSCA project next week. I have read a documentation about how to implement the MSCA. I would like to share some useful information and also keep them as a memorandum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;open-access&quot;&gt;Open Access&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two parts about Open Access (OA), namely OA for publication and OA for data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For publication OA, all peer-reviewed publications in this project should be either green OA or golden OA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Green OA means the beneficiaries can deposit the final peer-reviewed manuscript in a repository of their choice. Some good repository for MSCA could be https://www.openaire.eu/.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Golden OA means the publication can be in open access journals, or in hybrid journals that both sell subscriptions and offer the option of making individual articles openly accessible.
Links to the repositories in question must be provided in the system (Project Continuous Reporting).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For research data OA, one must submit a Data Management Plan within 6 months of the start of the action and the obligation to deposit the research data in a research data repository (e.g, Zenodo).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;acknowledgement-of-eu-funding&quot;&gt;Acknowledgement of EU Funding&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This project has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No [number].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;career-development-plan&quot;&gt;Career Development Plan&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Plan should define the training requirements, taking into account the research objectives and subsequent career goals. No template is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deliverables-to-report&quot;&gt;Deliverables to Report&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are two types of deliverables which may have to be reported:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Management Plan: a document outlining how the research data will be handled during your project, and after it is completed. It describes what data will be collected / generated; what methodology and standards are used; whether and how this data will be shared and/or made open; and how it will be curated and preserved. The DMP must be submitted within the first 6 months of the project. A DMP template is available at&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ethics requirements (if there were ethical issues)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unit-costs&quot;&gt;Unit Costs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two parts, namely Researcher Costs and Institutional Costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For researcher costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Living Allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobility Allowance. It is intended to cover the costs associated with the fact that you have moved to a different country in order to take up your position. This sum will not be audited and is flexible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Family Allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For institutional costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research, Training and Network Costs. This amount is intended to cover the costs associated with your project as
outlined in grant agreement, for example attending training courses, conferences, or when going on secondment. This should also  cover the cost of research (e.g. consumables), as appropriate, and can also be used to cover other related costs, such as visas.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Management and Indirect Costs. This is for university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;submission-of-reports&quot;&gt;Submission of Reports&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the report, you will be required to report on the scientific progress of your project, as well as your training and transfer of knowledge activities, secondments (if any), career development, the scientific management of the project, dissemination and communication activities, and on the project’s overall impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your report must be submitted within 60 days following the end date of the project. Submission of this report is a precondition for payment of the remaining amounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;submission-of-questionnaires&quot;&gt;Submission of Questionnaires&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funded researchers are requested to submit two questionnaires about their experience: one immediately following the completion of the project (“Evaluation Questionnaire”) and one two years later (“Follow-up Questionnaire”)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-marie-curie-alumni-association&quot;&gt;The Marie Curie Alumni Association&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Established as a not-for-profit organization in 2014, the Association offers opportunities for networking and peer exchange, an alumni directory, job offers, an events calendar, and other services of potential interest to IF researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="project management" />
			
			
				<category term="project management" />
			

			<published>2020-04-08T00:00:00+02:00</published>
		</entry>
	
</feed>