<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="/assets/xslt/atom.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="/assets/css/atom.css" ?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/</id>
	<title>MALOT</title>
	<updated>2023-03-20T14:52:48+08:00</updated>

	<subtitle>The EU MSCA Individual Fellowship</subtitle>

	
		
		<author>
			
				<name>Huan Li</name>
			
			
			
		</author>
	

	<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />

	<generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator>

	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/icde-bisim/</id>
			<title>[ICDE] Data Imputation for Sparse Radio Maps in Indoor Positioning</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/icde-bisim/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[ICDE] Data Imputation for Sparse Radio Maps in Indoor Positioning" />
			<updated>2023-03-19T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>a paper has been accepted by ICDE</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/icde-bisim/">&lt;p&gt;A new paper entitled “Data imputation for sparse radio maps in indoor positioning” by Xiao Li, Huan Li, Harry Kai-Ho Chan, Hua Lu, and Christian S. Jensen has been accepted by ICDE 2023.
Please checkout the paperswithcode at &lt;a href=&quot;https://cs.paperswithcode.com/paper/data-imputation-for-sparse-radio-maps-in&quot;&gt;https://cs.paperswithcode.com/paper/data-imputation-for-sparse-radio-maps-in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2023-03-19T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-vldb-sqm/</id>
			<title>[PVLDB] Edge Computing for Spatiotemporal Quantile Monitoring</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-vldb-sqm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[PVLDB] Edge Computing for Spatiotemporal Quantile Monitoring" />
			<updated>2022-04-18T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>a paper has been accepted by PVLDB</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-vldb-sqm/">&lt;p&gt;We have a research paper “Efficient and Error-Bounded Spatiotemporal Quantile Monitoring in Edge Computing Environments” accepted by PVLDB vol. 15. The abstract is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Underlying many types of data analytics, a spatiotemporal quantile monitoring (SQM) query continuously returns the quantiles of a data set observed in a spatiotemporal range. In this paper, we study SQM in an IoT-based edge computing environment, where concurrent SQM queries share the same infrastructure asynchronously. Our goal is to minimize query latency while providing result accuracy guarantees.
To this end, we design a processing framework that virtualizes edge-resident data sketches for quantile computing.
Within the framework, a coordinator edge node manages edge sketches and synchronizes the edge sketch processing and query executions.
The coordinator also controls the processed data fractions of edge sketches, which helps to achieve the optimal latency with error-bounded results for each single query.
To support concurrent queries, we employ a grid to decompose queries into subqueries and process them efficiently using shared edge sketches. We also devise a relaxing algorithm to converge to optimal latencies for those subqueries whose result errors are still bounded.
We evaluate our proposals extensively using two high-speed streaming datasets in a simulated IoT setting with edge nodes.
The results show that our proposals achieve efficient, scalable, and error-bounded SQM.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a work collaborated with collogues from SUSTECH and RUC. We look forward to presenting this work in VLDB 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2022-04-18T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-sigmod-tutorial/</id>
			<title>[SIGMOD] Tutorial on IoT Spatial Data Quality</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-sigmod-tutorial/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="[SIGMOD] Tutorial on IoT Spatial Data Quality" />
			<updated>2022-02-01T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Our proposal submitted to SIGMOD 2022 is now accepted</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-sigmod-tutorial/">&lt;p&gt;Our proposal entitled &lt;strong&gt;Spatial data quality in the IoT era: Management and exploitation&lt;/strong&gt; submitted to SIGMOD 2022 tutorial track has been accepted.
The tutorial utilizes the structure of our &lt;a href=&quot;https://longaspire.github.io/publication/sid/CSUR_2021_GreenOA.pdf&quot;&gt;ACM Computing Surveys paper&lt;/a&gt; and will be focusing on comparing the methodologies of representative works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope to release the full text and other relevant materials soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2022-02-01T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-outlier-subsequence/</id>
			<title>Knowledge Repository on Subsequence Outlier</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-outlier-subsequence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Knowledge Repository on Subsequence Outlier" />
			<updated>2021-12-02T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Useful resources for subsequence outlier detection</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-outlier-subsequence/">&lt;p&gt;Checkout our public repository on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/msca-malot/awesome-subsequence-outlier&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2021-12-02T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-csur/</id>
			<title>ACM Computing Surveys Paper on IoT Spatial Data Quality</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-csur/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ACM Computing Surveys Paper on IoT Spatial Data Quality" />
			<updated>2021-11-25T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Our full research paper is accepted by one of the flagship journals of the ACM</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-csur/">&lt;p&gt;Our long survey paper entitled &lt;strong&gt;Spatial Data Quality in the Internet of Things: Management, Exploitation, and Prospects&lt;/strong&gt; has been accepted by ACM Computing Surveys (IF: 10.3). Thanks to the great collaborations with Prof. Christian S. Jensen from AAU, Prof. Hua Lu from RUC, Prof. Muhammad Aamir Cheema from Monash U, and Prof. Bo Tang from SUSTECH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abstract of this paper is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;With the continued deployment of the Internet of Things (IoT), increasing volumes of devices are being deployed that emit massive spatially referenced data. Due in part to the dynamic, decentralized, and heterogeneous architecture of the IoT, the varying and often low quality of spatial IoT data (SID) presents challenges to applications built on top of this data. This survey aims to provide unique insight to practitioners who intend to develop IoT-enabled applications and to researchers who wish to conduct research that relates to data quality in the IoT setting. The survey offers an inventory analysis of major data quality dimensions in SID and covers significant data characteristics and associated quality considerations. The survey summarizes data quality related technologies from both task and technique perspectives. Organizing the technologies from the task perspective, it covers recent progress in SID quality management, encompassing location refinement, uncertainty elimination, outlier removal, fault correction, data integration, and data reduction; and it covers low-quality SID exploitation, encompassing querying, analysis, and decision-making techniques. Finally, the survey covers emerging trends and open issues concerning the quality of SID.*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A preprint under the Green OpenAccess protocol is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://longaspire.github.io/publication/sid/CSUR_2021_GreenOA.pdf&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2021-11-25T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/career%20development/2-pedagogy/</id>
			<title>University Pedagogy Training Start</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/career%20development/2-pedagogy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="University Pedagogy Training Start" />
			<updated>2021-01-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary></summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/career%20development/2-pedagogy/">&lt;p&gt;Last year in April I received an offer of Assistant Professor at the Department of Computer Science at Aalborg University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a follow-up, the university pedagogy training program is starting this year and for me it is anticipated to finish the training program within one year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this year, I will attend five compulsory courses and some selected courses, and finish a pedagogy report that addresses some specific issues in my teaching activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to finishing the training in a good shape.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="career development" />
			
			
				<category term="career development" />
			

			<published>2021-01-29T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-covid-iot/</id>
			<title>New COVID Survey Paper Published</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-covid-iot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New COVID Survey Paper Published" />
			<updated>2021-01-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Our COVID survey paper is now released at arXiv</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/research/1-covid-iot/">&lt;p&gt;Our survey paper &lt;em&gt;Impact of COVID-19 on Adoption of IoT in Different Sectors&lt;/em&gt; is now released at &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.07196&quot;&gt;arXiv&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abstract of this paper is as follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;COVID-19 has disrupted normal life and has enforced a substantial change in the policies, priorities and activities of individuals, organisations and governments. These changes are proving to be a catalyst for technology and innovation. In this paper, we discuss the pandemic’s impact on the adoption of the Internet of Things (IoT) in various broad sectors namely healthcare, smart homes, smart buildings, smart cities, transportation and industrial IoT. Our analysis of this impact on IoT adoption is based on interviews with many industry experts, a thorough research literature review and a careful examination of reports from leading consulting firms. For each of these sectors, we also provide the details of recent initiatives taken in the wake of COVID-19. We also highlight challenges that need to be addressed and important research directions that will facilitate accelerated IoT adoption in these sectors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This survey contains the most recent research papers about how IoT is incorporated into and affected by COVID-19 in vertical sectors such as healthcare, smart homes, smart buildings, smart cities, transportation, and industrial IoT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This paper has been submitted to IEEE Internet of Things Journal.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="research" />
			
			
				<category term="research" />
			

			<published>2021-01-29T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/1-quarter-progress/</id>
			<title>Quarter 1 Project Report</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/1-quarter-progress/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Quarter 1 Project Report" />
			<updated>2020-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>Q1 Progress Summary</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/1-quarter-progress/">&lt;p&gt;A quarter of the project’s time has passed. During this six months, we have been severely affected by COVID-19. The progress in the Q1 of the project includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Two survey papers (one has been finished and the other is still ongoing). The literature review is the first and the most fundamental part of this project’s research work. At present, a survey about COVID-19’s impact on IoT adoption is almost finished and will be submitted to IEEE Internet of Things Journal, and the other one on LoT data quality management is still developing;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Data Management Plan (DMP). The DMP that defines the collection, management and maintenance of the project data has been finished and submitted to the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Preliminary Career Development Plan (CDP). The CDP has been roughly finished and a discussion with supervisors will be carried out later. For career development, a position of Assistant Professor has been obtained from the Department of Computer Science at AAU. In addition, I have served as the session chair of VLDB 2020 and the external reviewers for several top conferences during this period. Preliminary academic collaboration with Monash, SDU (China), and  BUPT(China) has been established.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Deep participation of teaching activities at AAU CS department, including supervision of several groups and co-lecturing of a course. Moreover, the university pedagogy courses have been enrolled and will be started at the beginning of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Establishment of project website and social media accounts including GitHub and Twitter to disseminate research outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q2 will focus on finalizing the second survey paper, and the first regular research paper about data quality control.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="project management" />
			
			
				<category term="project management" />
			

			<published>2020-10-15T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/</id>
			<title>Plans of July 2020</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Plans of July 2020" />
			<updated>2020-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>The task planning of July 2020.</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/">&lt;p&gt;The plan of this month include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;discuss with the supervisor and finish the career development plan.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;start to write a survey paper about IoT data management and data quality control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="project management" />
			
			
				<category term="project management" />
			

			<published>2020-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<id>https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/</id>
			<title>Project Website is Now Online</title>
			<link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Website is Now Online" />
			<updated>2020-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated>

			
				
				<author>
					
						<name>huan li</name>
					
					
					
				</author>
			
			<summary>I am happy to announce that the project website is currently available.</summary>
			<content type="html" xml:base="https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/">&lt;p&gt;Today is the last day of June, and I am very happy to announce that the project website is available from now on. We will continue to publish any news and results in this venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website is powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;JEKYLL&lt;/a&gt; based on the theme &lt;a href=&quot;http://phlow.github.io/feeling-responsive/&quot;&gt;FEELING RESPONSIVE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>

			
				<category term="dissemination" />
			
			
				<category term="dissemination" />
			

			<published>2020-06-30T00:00:00+08:00</published>
		</entry>
	
</feed>