<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://msca-malot.github.io/assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="https://msca-malot.github.io/assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>MALOT</title>
		<description>The EU MSCA Project</description>
		<link>https://msca-malot.github.io/</link>
		<atom:link href="https://msca-malot.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Plans of July 2020</title>
				<link>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;This plan this month will include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;discuss with the supervisor and finish the career development plan.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;start to write a survey paper about IoT data management and data quality control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/2-plans-july-2020/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Project Website is Now Online</title>
				<link>https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the last day of June, and I am very happy to announce that the project website is available from now on. We will continue to publish any news and results in this venue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website is powered by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;JEKYLL&lt;/a&gt; based on the theme &lt;a href=&quot;http://phlow.github.io/feeling-responsive/&quot;&gt;FEELING RESPONSIVE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://msca-malot.github.io/dissemination/1-website-start/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Get into MSCA Implementation</title>
				<link>https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/get-into-implementation/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;I am excited and looking forward to starting my MSCA project next week. I have read a documentation about how to implement the MSCA. I would like to share some useful information and also keep them as a memorandum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;open-access&quot;&gt;Open Access&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two parts about Open Access (OA), namely OA for publication and OA for data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For publication OA, all peer-reviewed publications in this project should be either green OA or golden OA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Green OA means the beneficiaries can deposit the final peer-reviewed manuscript in a repository of their choice. Some good repository for MSCA could be https://www.openaire.eu/.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Golden OA means the publication can be in open access journals, or in hybrid journals that both sell subscriptions and offer the option of making individual articles openly accessible.
Links to the repositories in question must be provided in the system (Project Continuous Reporting).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For research data OA, one must submit a Data Management Plan within 6 months of the start of the action and the obligation to deposit the research data in a research data repository (e.g, Zenodo).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;acknowledgement-of-eu-funding&quot;&gt;Acknowledgement of EU Funding&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This project has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No [number].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;career-development-plan&quot;&gt;Career Development Plan&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Plan should define the training requirements, taking into account the research objectives and subsequent career goals. No template is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deliverables-to-report&quot;&gt;Deliverables to Report&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;there are two types of deliverables which may have to be reported:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data Management Plan: a document outlining how the research data will be handled during your project, and after it is completed. It describes what data will be collected / generated; what methodology and standards are used; whether and how this data will be shared and/or made open; and how it will be curated and preserved. The DMP must be submitted within the first 6 months of the project. A DMP template is available at&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ethics requirements (if there were ethical issues)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unit-costs&quot;&gt;Unit Costs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two parts, namely Researcher Costs and Institutional Costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For researcher costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Living Allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mobility Allowance. It is intended to cover the costs associated with the fact that you have moved to a different country in order to take up your position. This sum will not be audited and is flexible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Family Allowance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For institutional costs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research, Training and Network Costs. This amount is intended to cover the costs associated with your project as
outlined in grant agreement, for example attending training courses, conferences, or when going on secondment. This should also  cover the cost of research (e.g. consumables), as appropriate, and can also be used to cover other related costs, such as visas.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Management and Indirect Costs. This is for university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;submission-of-reports&quot;&gt;Submission of Reports&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the report, you will be required to report on the scientific progress of your project, as well as your training and transfer of knowledge activities, secondments (if any), career development, the scientific management of the project, dissemination and communication activities, and on the project’s overall impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your report must be submitted within 60 days following the end date of the project. Submission of this report is a precondition for payment of the remaining amounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;submission-of-questionnaires&quot;&gt;Submission of Questionnaires&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The funded researchers are requested to submit two questionnaires about their experience: one immediately following the completion of the project (“Evaluation Questionnaire”) and one two years later (“Follow-up Questionnaire”)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-marie-curie-alumni-association&quot;&gt;The Marie Curie Alumni Association&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Established as a not-for-profit organization in 2014, the Association offers opportunities for networking and peer exchange, an alumni directory, job offers, an events calendar, and other services of potential interest to IF researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://msca-malot.github.io/project%20management/get-into-implementation/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
